cuteoverload.com 2013-12-21

# Privacy Policy — Cute Overload

Privaceh! Policeh!

Let’s get this party started:

This privacy policy applies to transactions and activities in which you engage and data gathered only on the Cute Overload web site “[http://www.cuteoverload.com&#8221](http://www.cuteoverload.com%26/#8221); (the “Site”). This privacy policy does not apply to any other web site or to any offline contact between you and Cute Overload. Please review this privacy policy periodically because we modify it from time to time. Each time you visit this Site or provide us with information through the Site, by doing so you are accepting practices described in the privacy policy in effect at that time.

You are also accepting our Terms of Use (they are also really cute). We limit use of the Site to adults who are at least 13 years of age and we do not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If we learn that a submission or post is by a person under the age of 13, we will remove the material.

Let’s put that another way so we’re really clear. Cute Overload requires all users to be at least thirteen (13) years old to use this Site.

Gosh, we’re serious about this! Let’s keep going.

**Information We Collect**  
As you use the Site Services (as defined in the Terms of Use), we may collect your name and email, as well as other personally identifiable information (“User Data”). We may send you information under limited circumstances, including compliance with legal notices, including subpoenas, to notify you of a change in service, to authenticate your User Data, or to update you on services. We may also collect personal information if you provide it in feedback or comments or contact us directly.

Like most interactive websites, each time you visit the Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize the site for you and to diagnose problems with our site we use your IP address which helps us identify you and gather broad demographic information about you and where you logged in from. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your activity on the Site and to enhance your experience on the Site. We may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Third party advertisers and/or service providers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser should you click through to their web sites. If you wish to disable these cookies, the help portion of the tool bar on most browsers will tell you how to do that.  
In order to operate the Site, accept and post your image and/or video submissions, and fulfill product orders you may make, and allow you to post comments about images and videos on the Site, we collect information including personal contact information and demographic information. Contact information can be used to contact you directly without going through the Site and may include your full name, postal address, phone number, or e-mail address. We do not store credit card or other financial information. Credit Card transactions are transmitted directly through a third party payment service. Demographic information is information that you submit or we collect that is neither personal nor financial; this may include but is not limited to your zip code, postal code, or hometown.

**Don’t Be Silly!**  
Please use common sense when posting a comment. Both the comment and your email address will be publicly available. Please do not post any personal information that you expect to keep private. For more information about posting comments and submitting content, please see our Terms of Use.

**Circumstances Under Which We Might Release Information**  
Cute Overload may disclose information about its users, including personal information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes. We may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in response to a valid legal request, or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms of Use.

We reserve the right to transfer your submitted information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Cute Overload such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**External Links**  
The Cute Overload Site may contain links to other websites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information.

**Security**  
Cute Overload uses industry standard measures to protect your information so that it is not made available to unauthorized parties.  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us through the Site or at the following address: Cute Overload, Inc, attn: Privacy Policy, 2120 Avy, #7461, Menlo Park, CA, 94026.
